<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <string name="tab_text_1">Historical</string>
    <string name="tab_text_2">Event</string>
    <string name="tab_text_3">restaurant</string>
    <string name="tab_text_4">RentCar</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="attending">ARE YOU ATTENDING</string>
    <string name="event1data">10/10/2019</string>
    <string name="event1address">10 Westpoint Arena</string>
    <string name="event2data">5/2/2019</string>
    <string name="event2address">43 hhbhdchdhyhgy</string>
    <string name="AQUADIVERS">AQUA DIVERS</string>
    <string name="pyramidsdetail">"
AQUA DIVERS is situated within a 3 stars hotel with private swimming pool on Mashraba beach in Dahab, overlooking the Gulf of Aqaba.As a company, we pride ourselves in providing the highest personal and professional service to our guests in a relaxing environment.
We offer a complete range of diving packages, safaris and PADI courses from your first breaths to dive professional, as well as accommodation to suit most budgets. Our team of friendly staff and experienced, multilingual instructors will ensure your diving adventure is both safe and fun.\n ABOUT US \n A fantastic variety of amazing dive sites are scattered along the golden coast of Dahab.
Being part of the marine protectorate, the fringing reefs offer an impressive array of hard and soft corals which are home to a wealth of fascinating marine life.Most sites offer perfect conditions for beginners and experienced divers alike, with easy shore entries and usually reached by a short jeep ride.Camel safaris are an exciting way to explore some of the more remote sites and regular boat safaris are scheduled to Ras Mohamed, the wreck of the Thistlegorm and Tiran Islands. You will find AQUA DIVERS very flexible and accommodating when it comes to arranging your diving holiday"</string>
    <string name="luxortitle">Luxor,s Karnak Temple and the Valley of the Kings</string>
    <string name="luxordetail">"Famed for the Valley of the Kings, Karnak Temple, and the Memorial Temple of Hatshepsut, the Nile-side town of Luxor in Upper Egypt has a glut of tourist attractions. This is ancient Thebes, powerbase of the New Kingdom pharaohs, and home to more sights than most can see on one visit. While the East Bank brims with vibrant souk action, the quieter West Bank is home to a bundle of tombs and temples that has been called the biggest open air museum in the world. Spend a few days here exploring the colorful wall art of the tombs and gazing in awe at the colossal columns in the temples, and you'll see why Luxor continues to fascinate historians and archaeologists."</string>
    <string name="rentcarname">Alamo</string>
    <string name="rentcaraddress">"1501 NW 49th St, Suite 100\n Fort Lauderdale, FL 33309\n USA"</string>
    <string name="rentcaraphone"> 1 8887498541</string>
    <string name="rentcaraworkTime">24H</string>
    <string name="restaurantname">"Belmond Le Manoir aux Quat'Saisons"</string>
    <string name="restaurantdetail">"Drinks, Breakfast, Lunch, Dinner, Late Night "</string>
    <string name="restaurantaddress">" Church Road, Great Milton OX44 7PD, England  "</string>
    <string name="restaurantphone">+44 184278881</string>
    <string name="restaurantemail">rdr@hh.com</string>
    <string name="restaurantworkTime">1:00 PM-2:00 AM</string>
</resources>
